Zbarasheuski, Stanislau (Stan)

216-534-7763, svz.zero@gmail.com, Linked In, GitHub, Website(sxz.cloud)

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Aspiring scientist, technologist; experienced in technical and scientific topics. Academic and hands on experience in Computer Networking & Engineering, Material Science & Engineering, Manufacturing & Design.

Six years in metallurgy, and microscopy laboratories. Configured and installed Cisco and other programmable controllers since (2007). Professional background ranging from to \$2.6 million government research projects to start-ups; that generated revenue of more than \$2.4 million – in sales – the first year of incorporation.

Always looking for knowledge and skill growth in Technology and the Sciences.

EDUCATION

Digital Transformation program, Massachusetts Institute of Technology

Focus: Al and IoT to Cloud, Blockchain, and Cybersecurity

Associates of Arts and Science, Cuyahoga Community College, Ohio

Focus: Calculus and Chemistry

Non-Degree, Case Western Reserve University, Ohio

Focus: Chemistry, Physics, Material Science & Engineering

Computer Networking & Engineering, Lakeland Community College, Ohio

Focus: Networking (IT), PC Repair, cabling, and communications (CCNA & CCNP)

Computer, Networking, Electronics, EXCEL T.E.C.C./Mayfield School, Ohio 2007-2009

Focus: Computer Networking (IT), Electronics, Programming (honor roll standing & awards)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Genius One, Inc., Cleveland Ohio

2017-2018

R&D Engineer; Tasked to optimize heat exchange between a solid and a fluid with minimal impedance to the flow rate.

- Drafted, Prototyped, Presented Pre-Production Consumer Products; ceramic, metallic, and polymers
- Found Domestic Electro Chemist; improved consistency in quality and savings of \$0.38/part; ≈68.4k/year
- Managed personnel to accomplish daily and monthly quota; steady numbers with consistent quality
- IT & Network Security; removed malware & located source & target PC of bot-program's network traffic
- Eliminated a work station by advising acquisition of equipment; more fluid workday for the employees



CWRU; Department of Material Science & Engineering; Foundry, Cleveland Ohio 2013-2017 Laboratory Technician; worked on multiple projects from multilayer depositions (4 methods of 3D printing) of martensite steel on to H13 tool-steel substrate to surface coatings for high temperature application.

- Analyses of; alloys, boundaries, inclusions and areas of interest, heat affected zones
- Metallurgy; prepared chemicals, polished & etched samples, examined grain crystals & boundaries
- Microscopy; captured optical photographs, used scanning electron microscopes (SEMs); element analises
- Produced lab reports, presented derived data for academic publications and/or client company's reports
- Trained students on equipment operation and processing of samples
- Maintained one of the kind equipment, retro fitted equipment to link with modern PC
- Ordered Manufacturing of custom parts
- Helped with student projects requiering high temperachor equipment or materials



CWRU, Department of Material Science & Engineering, Cleveland Ohio

2011-2013

Laboratory Intern; worked with a passionate team funded by an <u>ARPA-E</u> grant. Aided as needed postdoctoral researchers, graduate students, and any task that was entrusted to me from the Principal investor.

- Sintered, Brazed, Arc Welded, Micro Welded, Spot Welded, Soldered, Anodized, Oxidation Reduction
- Mixed high purity, extremely fine, elemental powders to be sintered; at times to 0 +/- 4μg accuracy
- Used X-Ray diffraction, Thermal Gravitational Analysis, and Electron Microscopy equipment
- Operated ultra-high vacuum equipment; at times in combination with custom backfilled atmospheres
- Prepared surfaces of desired samples via micro polishing, chemical etching, or plasma etching methods
- Measured the affected surface area; ether with a caliper and mathematics or image processing and computational software
- Assembled laboratory & prototyping equipment, assembled & packaged product prototypes; several
 configurations were used to maximize density per unit of volume for sponsor revue and more
 conventional form for electrical engineering designation

AWARDS AND CERTIFICATES

 Massachusetts Institute of Technology; <u>Digital transformation</u> 	2019
Fire Hydrant Award	2019
 NASA Robotic Mining Competition, certificate of participant 	
2013 & 2014	
 <u>Collegiate Cyber Defense Competition</u>, certificate of participant 	2013
 CCNA Exploration (Cisco Networking Award) 	2010
 Computers, Networking & Electronics 	2009

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Proficiency with; Microsoft & Open Office, Linux Distributions, Windows OSes, Adobe Photoshop, Google Apps CAD; SolidWorks, LTSPICE, Slicers (3D printers), SketchUp, Openrocket, EveryCircuit Programmed in; HTML, JavaScript, Dream Weaver, Python, C++, VB, Dark Basic Electronics; designed, manufactured, & repaired circuits, industrial and residential electrical experience

LANGUAGES

English Russian Polish Belarusian Spanish(beginner)

HOBBIES

Rocketry; telemetry, structures, propulsion (co founded a club "<u>Case Rocket Team</u>")
Robotics; automation, navigation, 3D printing (co founded a club "<u>CWRUbotix</u>")
Hacking at; drones, Kali Linux (collaborated on IT competitions and hackathons projects)

10 Year Experience Summary R&D Robotics Programming Management